{
    "subject": "resource/J._D._Hayworth",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "J. D. Hayworth",
    "human_readable": "J. D. Hayworth is commonly known as J. D. Hayworth.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9877597689628601,
            "question": "What is J. D. Hayworth commonly known as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.98518306016922,
            "question": "What is the commonly recognized name of J. D. Hayworth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9839923977851868,
            "question": "Is there another name by which J.D. Hayworth is known?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9704719185829163,
            "question": "Which name is used most frequently for J.D. Hayworth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.96320641040802,
            "question": "What is the familiar name associated with J. D. Hayworth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9583293795585632,
            "question": "What name is most widely used when talking about J.D. Hayworth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9412353038787842,
            "question": "What is the most popular way to refer to J. D. Hayworth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9163661599159241,
            "question": "If someone wanted to refer to J. D. Hayworth in a common way, what would they say?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9085640907287598,
            "question": "How is J. D. Hayworth generally addressed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8872024416923523,
            "question": "How would you typically refer to J. D. Hayworth in conversation?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=J. D. Hayworth is commonly known as J. D. Hayworth.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3357_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is J. D. Hayworth generally addressed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3357_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If someone wanted to refer to J. D. Hayworth in a common way, what would they say?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3357_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the most popular way to refer to J. D. Hayworth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3357_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3357_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3357_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3357_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3357_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3357_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3357_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3357_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3357_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3357_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3357_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, I will evaluate the triple:\n\n**Triple:** J. D. Hayworth is commonly known as J. D. Hayworth.\n\n**Evaluation:** The documents provide information about a person named J. D. Hayworth, and in one of them (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3357/re-ranker-msmarco/49.txt), it is stated that \"John David Hayworth, Jr. (born July 12, 1958), usually known as J. D. Hayworth...\" This suggests that John David Hayworth, Jr. is commonly known as J. D. Hayworth.\n\nTherefore:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly refer to JD Hayworth using the name \"J.D. Hayworth\" or \"JD Hayworth,\" which supports the statement that he is commonly known by this name."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}